I'm not going to pay for today's bill.
Thank you!
Sakai, look over there.
Now!
I'm going to pay for today's bill.
What?
Hello, everyone.
We are TOKIMEKI SENNENBU.
We are here to celebrate the release of
our single, ABXII.
We are collaborating with a restaurant
called ANRAKUTEN.
Let's eat a lot of meat and dance
together to aim for the unbeatable super
body.
Did you understand?
Yes.
What are these five people doing today?
What?
What did she say?
What's wrong with you?
You did a good job. I've been waiting
for you.
I'm wearing an apron.
What's wrong?
This is a Yakiniku restaurant.
It's called Enraku.
It's a Yakiniku restaurant.
It's a restaurant in the Anrakutei
line.
It opened in Adachi, Tokyo in September
this year.
It's called Enraku.
Enraku.
I'm going to ask you to work to show
you the charm of Enraku.
Do you know what this is?
It's a drama about delusional love.
Yeah!
I'm going to ask you to act while
thinking about the script of the drama.
There are four elements in the box.
You'll act based on the four elements.
I'd like you to confess to me at the
end.
Please connect it to me.
I see.
I've been wondering about something.
What is it?
Did you eat meat first?
Did you hide the meat here?
I haven't ordered it yet.
I ate a little kalbi.
I'm sorry.
Actually, I took off my soy sauce.
It's swollen.
It's rare, so please watch it a lot.
There's no meat in it.
The top pattern is Tanamin.
Please listen to the situation box.
I'll listen to it.
The first one is the situation.
The meat is cut at the store.
The soup is made after receiving the
order.
The original is the best.
What?
Situation.
What kind of situation is this?
It's a natural situation.
The next one is the item.
It's a member of the same age group.
The next one is the member of the same
age group.
It's Hirari Yoshikawa.
It's the last scene.
The last scene.
She is holding her hand gently.
What should I do?
The last scene.
Let's say it together.
Ready, set, go.
I'm finally here.
I ordered Ishiyaki bibimbap.
It looks delicious.
You must be hungry.
I'm starving.
I'll take care of you.
Where do you take me?
I thought that I could eat as much as I
want with Tanamin.
The staff here is very careful about
the freshness of the food.
So, this is also delicious.
I'll try it.
Are you okay?
What happened?
I think it'll be more delicious because
you're here.
Thank you.
Don't you eat?
Let's eat together.
This is a mask.
It's cute.
It's like a tent.
Do you want to do it?
It's like you are going to do it.
I can do it.
I want you to do it.
What is that?
What is going on?
It's embarrassing.
It's okay.
Ready, go.
What are you doing?
Hey.
I don't do it with a normal couple.
It's delicious.
It's the best when it's freshly made.
My hands are...
It's embarrassing.
What's wrong?
I'm getting hot because I ate bibimbap.
I want you to accept my love for you.
Of course.
I'll be happy from now on.
Stop.
I'll add a situation.
Please be careful.
P.O.
Didn't you talk to a girl I don't know
yesterday?
Me?
I don't know you.
It's the first time I've seen you.
Finally.
I don't talk to girls other than
Kanami.
Really?
Yes.
You were so close to me.
I was hot when I ate bibimbap.
Why did you change the subject?
You didn't blow on me when I ate
bibimbap.
I wanted you to blow on me.
Because you are a girl.
I won't pay for today's bill.
Thank you.
You are great.
I remember that.
I cut it.
Because you are a girl.
I will blow on you.
I have to talk about the culture
festival.
You were talking about it.
I don't like it.
Please pull the box.
I will go to the train station.
By chance on a holiday day浜亜山
Disco shift
Since it is a astronomer, you will be
nervous.
I'm nervous.
What are you going to do?
I'm going to do the second one.
I'm going to do it.
Haruka is going to do it.
The last scene.
Wait.
I'm going to do it.
What are you going to do?
What kind of person is Bambi?
Bambi is a woman.
What about Oharu?
Oharu is a woman, too.
Hitoka is a man.
Ready, go!
It's here!
It looks delicious.
It's thick and looks delicious.
It sounds good.
It's good.
It's very thick.
I invited you to eat Yakiniku today.
We are good friends.
I want to talk to you.
But we don't go to Yakiniku often.
We don't go to Yakiniku often.
So, I want to talk to you.
What do you want to talk about?
I have a question.
Who do you think is cool?
I think you are cool.
Thank you.
I think Sakaya is cool.
I know.
You have a different impression.
I think Sakaya is cool.
Do you like it?
Wow, that's great.
There is a music festival soon.
Yes, there is.
I want to practice more and get along
with the athletes.
I think you can get along with them.
I grilled some meat.
Oh, it looks delicious.
It's hot.
So, I want you to cooperate with me.
Cooperate?
I don't know what you are aiming for.
It's OK.
I'm ready.
Can I eat this?
Let's eat!
She is eating a lot.
It's good.
Is it hot?
No, it's not.
It's so good.
Wait.
Bambi and Haruka, what are you doing?
We are doing a face mask.
I want to try it too.
I'll try Bambi's face mask.
Do you want to eat it?
Can I?
I just finished a soccer tournament.
I won.
Thank you.
Can you do it for me?
I'm glad that I can do it for you.
What were you talking about?
It's almost time for the test.
I haven't studied at all.
But you can do it.
Teach me.
Can I?
Teach me how to study.
Then, I'll do it.
I'll do it next time.
Let's start the test.
High car.
I was curious about your words.
Can I go to that seat?
Yes.
OK.
I'll go there.
I'm going to go there.
You were cute today.
What?
You were always cute.
When are you going to introduce me to
your girlfriend?
Anytime.
I'll do it tomorrow.
I'll do it.
After school.
I want to do barbie and Rike.
Rike is too much.
Really? But I'm not good at it.
You're rude to me.
That's right.
I want to do it at the barbershop.
What?
We're good friends.
That's good.
We went to the same elementary school.
We've been together all the time.
We're in the same elementary school.
Do you have a crush on someone?
Yes.
What?
Who?
Haruka.
I have a crush on Oharu.
Do you know who she is?
I don't know.
I don't know her.
We are childhood friends.
Oh, we are childhood friends.
Let's experience childhood friendship.
Let's do it.
Childhood friendship? No way.
Let's go over there.
Over there?
We are childhood friends.
Oh, I see.
We are getting along well.
We are childhood friends.
We are like a couple.
Right.
Where are you looking at?
Can I go back there?
No, no, no.
Why?
No, no.
Sakai, look over there.
Now.
I like you.
Please subscribe to this channel.
Oh!
I won!
I was wondering how long you would keep
going.
I was so nervous.
Hitoka, you are the third.
Please choose from the box.
I will draw.
What is it?
School's end.
School's end?
Item?
Yukie-chan.
I will draw.
Kogetsu Miyako.
Thank you very much.
You can see the blue spring.
I'll take one more picture.
The last scene.
Can I hug you?
Hug?
Hug at a barbeque restaurant?
What is your gender?
I'm a girl and my name is Koizumi.
I like Koizumi and I'm a helper.
Let's start.
Ready, action!
What should I do?
I finally asked him out.
But I'm too nervous to talk to him.
I'm nervous, but I'll do my best.
Sorry to keep you waiting.
It looks delicious.
Can I eat this first?
Sure.
Let's eat.
Itadakimasu.
It looks delicious.
Is it delicious?
It's a little spicy, but it's
delicious.
It's a spicy level that I can eat.
Is that so?
This soup is made after ordering.
I see.
That's why it's so delicious.
It's hot and delicious.
Do you want to eat this?
I'll take it for you.
Thank you.
I think it will be more delicious.
Don't say that.
Is it good?
It's good, right?
I'm sorry, I have to go.
I'm sorry.
See you later.
Hey.
Yes?
I just gave you a bite.
Yes.
Can you do me a favor?
Oh.
I'm sorry.
Look at me.
Close your eyes.
Wow!
I love you.
I did it!
I'm so happy.
I'm embarrassed.
What should I do?
How was it?
Good.
I got a barometer.
Please subscribe to my channel.
I don't know what I'm talking about.
I'm so nervous.
We have a special prize for you.
I haven't heard about it.
The first place is...
I want to do live with you.
I will definitely show you a more
powerful appearance than last year.
I'm so happy that Senzenburi is really
a good band to support.
Our mystery story has just begun.
I think there is no limit to the
possibilities of the future if you look
at it with a mirror.
If you are with Senzenburi and the
members, you can definitely make a big
wall into a small wall.
We believe in that.
So, please wait for us. Nakano-san
Plus!
Dash! Dash! Let's chase our dreams!
Dash! Dash! Dash! Never wake up from
this dream!
With you, I can make my dreams come
true!
I can be happy!
If you want to be a hero, shape up,
shape up, shake a leg, shape up
My goal is to be as big as a three-
legged apple
Lose weight, lose weight, lose weight,
don't let your guard down
Let's go, do me, do me, yo! Do me, do
me, yo!
Don't show me your true feelings
Do me, do me, yo! Do me, do me, yo!
Don't make a fool of me, I'm in a good
mood!